How often do you go to the park?
你多久去一次公园？
Is it part of your everyday life, or a trip that you plan?
它是你日常生活的一部分，还是你计划的一次出行？
Many large urban parks are situated far from where people live, meaning they are a destination for planned visits rather than everyday life.
许多大型城市公园离人们居住的地方很远，这意味着它们是计划出行的目的地，而不是日常生活的一部分。
For example, only 14% of the population of Los Angeles have a park within walking distance.
例如，洛杉矶只有14%的人口在步行距离内有公园。
Also, the distribution of such parks is often relatively unequal, meaning that they benefit some areas and groups of people much more than others.
此外，这类公园的分布往往相对不均，这意味着它们对某些地区和群体的益处远大于其他地区和群体。
A number of studies have shown that it is often disadvantaged neighbourhoods that lack easy access to green spaces.
许多研究表明，往往是贫困社区很难接触到绿地。
It's rarely practical to address this by creating large new parks, but designating small parcels of land, empty lots, or even parts of quiet streets as pocket parks can have a major impact on residents' quality of life.
通过建造大型新公园来解决这个问题通常不现实，但将小块土地、空地、甚至安静街道的一部分指定为袖珍公园，可以对居民的生活质量产生重大影响。
Often no larger than a few tennis courts and located within neighbourhoods close to where people live, these green spaces can strengthen community bonds.
这些绿地通常不超过几个网球场大小，位于靠近人们居住的社区内，可以加强社区联系。
They provide a place to meet neighbours, or a play area for children.
它们提供了与邻居见面的场所，或者为孩子们提供了游乐区。
Green gyms or ball game areas can give local people a space to exercise in, improving public health outcomes.
绿色健身房或球类运动区可以为当地居民提供锻炼空间，改善公众健康。
Local businesses can use spaces to promote their products or organise events to help them grow.
当地企业可以利用这些空间推广产品或组织活动以帮助其发展。
A study by the University of Philadelphia, showed that crime was reduced in neighbourhoods with pocket parks, compared to those which left empty spaces derelict.
费城大学的一项研究表明，与那些让空地荒废的社区相比，拥有袖珍公园的社区犯罪率降低了。
Studies report that where space is used to make pocket parks, communities feel greater ownership of and attachment towards their neighbourhood.
研究报告称，在利用空间建造袖珍公园的地方，社区居民们对其社区有更强的主人翁意识和归属感。
As well as benefits for the human population, an increase in green space can benefit the local environment.
除了对人群的益处，绿地的增加也有利于当地环境。
Pocket parks can act as stepping stones, allowing wildlife to travel across the city, as well as providing habitats for different species.
袖珍公园可以充当踏脚石，让野生动物穿越城市，同时也为不同物种提供栖息地。
Parks provide increased tree canopy cover, offering shade which can counteract urban heat island effects, helping to reduce temperatures.
公园增加了树冠覆盖，提供遮荫，可以抵消城市热岛效应，帮助降低温度。
Trees also help to reduce air pollution, and green space allows water to drain away, reducing flood risks.
树木还有助于减少空气污染，绿地可以让水排走，降低洪水风险。
Could pocket parks be a relatively cheap way to strengthen communities and improve local environments?
袖珍公园能否成为改善社区和当地环境的一种相对廉价的方式？